Hey,
everyone. So, I want to talk about,
uh, how I'm making the,
uhm,
an evaluation system. And, basically,
a CX agent builder and evaluation system,
basically, right? And, uhm,
as part of this whole journey, today,
I want to talk about how can I generate a really good dataset
against which I can evaluate. Or test my CX
agent that I want to deploy for my customers,
which are basically businesses in, uh,
B2C domain, primarily, but it can be more than that as well,
right? So, as part of that,
uhm, so if you, just a quick background for that. Good context.
We, uh, basically have, uh,
by CX agent I mean is like something which is,
uh, sitting on your website on your,
uh, as a widget, uh,
on your, uh, for example, here,
this is our website and, uh, you can click on this and,
uh, it sits like a chat widget where you can say,
hey, uh,
tell me about your
company,
TARS. So,
uh, it'll just respond to me, uh,
tell me about the company and, uh,
obviously, TARS is a delivery service.
We're known for delivering high,
highly personalized, result-driven AI agent that automate conversations and boost engagements.
So, yeah, that is what we do. We basically,
uh,
make these, uh, AI agents,
which are basically sitting on your website as a widget or on your,
uh, uhm,
WhatsApp number, on your email. So, it's like a CX solution.
It's like pretty much typical CX solution,
nothing super fancy there, uh,
but very, uh, important problem.
Uhm,
so, in this one, I'm going to,
so you need to have an agent which will basically answer to users' questions
and basically help them with whatever they want, right? So,
very broadly speaking, uhm,
basically, the kind of customers that will come there,
especially, either in the, uh,
pre-sale stage, they, the, the agent is supposed to basically help them,
you know, understand the product and do, you know, some kind of,
you know, sales, sales or selling, or, you know, consultative selling and if they're
already a customer, uh, then it will basically help them,
you know, in terms of support and, uh,
understanding what they want and helping them and, uh,
maybe, uh,
if, uh, if, uh, configured, it can be in the expansion mode as well,
where, uh, it will try to up-sell and cross-sell,
those kind of stuff, right? But anyway, that's what it Whatever it is doing,
it's basically interacting with the customer to help them answer questions or
to do things on their behalf. So, this is a very broad level of
two things, which, uh, I'm just putting in,
this is what basically the CX agents do essentially for the CX use cases,
basically. Customer experience use case, which is customer support or customer sales,
right? Um, online sales or digital sales kind of,
uh, channel, right?
So, um,
so as part of this thing, whenever there's an interaction happening,
there's either customers asking a question or they're asking for some request to
take some action. For example, uh, help them book a meeting or
send an email or create a ticket or,
uh, uh, file a complaint or make a sale.
You know, purchase something or whatever, right? So these are all things like actions
that they want to get done on their behalf. But the other aspect is
they want to understand about how the product works, uh,
what is the pricing looks like, and, uh,
how can, uh, they use it, do they have this feature,
you know, or how do you solve it. So they have a lot of
questions about, uhm, in the pre-sales stage and after that, how,
uh, I'm having issues with this particular feature, you know, how can I fix
it, or, do we have this feature,
I cannot find it, right, or I I don't know how to do it,
right, or maybe I maybe, uhm,
uh, can I, you know, add more team members, uh,
and do we have a team plan, something like that, I want to upgrade,
you know, those kind of things. Uh,
basically, any of those things will be a mix of two
of these atomic tasks, you know, in my head, uh,
to keep things simple, which is one, to either ask questions or take some
actions, right? So, as part of the first thing,
which is to ask questions and get a really good response and,
and, uh, very, uhm,
detailed and very, uh, uhm, uh, helpful response.
So in that case, uhm, uh,
the most important tool or most important thing is basically knowledge retrieval and,
and basically that's what, uh, that's why in my oral,
overall CX agent system, I'm much more focused or I'm,
I'm, I'm, I'm focusing a lot right now and as part of this development
journey to on retrievers essentially,
right? So retriever is basically something like where you give
it a bunch of documents, which are the KB that has six documents,
it has other documents. So as you get a different different,
uh, uh, knowledge bases,
for each of the knowledge base, you can create different kind of retrievers.
And, uh,
so again, I'll not go into this in detail, but basically you can create
all the configuration about how it works. How it is indexed,
or how you can query it, uh,
you know, and different approaches and different rag, these are basically different rag approaches,
but, uh, it has some other, uh,
kind of text, um, basically full text search as well as VN25,
right, you can have hybrid search, and for each of them you can set
the corresponding password. And you can also add refinement to
do re-ranking, threshold-based,
uh, refinement,
deduplication, so there are different techniques,
you know, that you can use to do refinement, and then finally you can
query it. create this retriever, so this is very customisable retrievalment
system, so again, I'll, uh,
not go too deep into this thing, in this, uh,
call, or in this video. So,
I'll come back to her. Um, dataset generation and,
so, it's part of figuring out what is a good retrieval,
and, uh, for a dataset and in general,
and how does it work. So, we need to evaluate the retrieval,
and retrieval evaluation is something very important,
and, uh, I don't think it's going to influence to be,
uh, I mean, there's always going to be,
maybe there's a technique which comes and which works really well,
and, uh, there's no need for all this system.
We just use that. Maybe that will happen, uh,
and that, that will be great, but until that does not happen,
we have to have this evaluation system. You can try a lot of things,
right, and especially when you are working in a very diverse set of data
set, uh, within the one organization itself,
right, and definitely across different industries.
So, for example, within, let's say, um,
finance company, we have documents like,
uh, SEC filings. You will have,
uh, financial, uh, sheets,
right, uh, spreadsheets, and you will have,
uh, documents, reports, annual reports,
those kind of stuff, right? So, all of them have very different kind of,
uh, like data format, and,
uh, ideally, we would want, uh, to be able to read all of those
things, so that's something, you know, we are building these retrievers for,
and knowledge base section for, so again, I'm not going to do that.
So, uh,
but the important thing is that across all of these things,
you need to be able to evaluate which one is working well for your
use case for your dataset, right? So,
for that, I have built this evaluation system,
retriever evaluation system, and for retrieval evaluation,
I need a dataset against which to do evaluation,
and this basically is a dataset, uh,
this video is about how that dataset I am building and,
uh, how is it, uh,
going to help, right? So,
cough cough cough
hmm
jar boards are great! So these are, basically,
what I have done is, I have given it,
uh,
it starts with the Knowledge base, so I, I have taken,
I a small list. I have a list of six documents,
so that we can, uh,
uh, review it much more easily, but you can do it for larger documents
as well, it's just going to take some time, we are going to process
all of that. So I have been working with six documents here,
these are mostly our own internal, like,
uh, internal docs, so I just kept a small number of documents,
so I made a small corpus, and I have,
uh, so I can create a new generation like this,
uh, so this is an existing dataset,
you know, with 48 questions, so, uhm,
I'll come back to the generation, but it'll be me show you quickly what
it is. So, what happens is,
within this, uh, uh, generation,
I need to create, this is a 48 questions,
you know, were, were generated, and there were 6 documents,
so what it does is that it goes to each of these documents,
and, uhm, and tries to, basically generates a,
a question, which we would want to evaluate against,
for example, these questions are basically user questions,
so, this is one example is how to make the live chat come to
my task conversations, right, this is actually user questions,
I'll again, go to this new generation I'll talk about,
ah, basically here you can add,
ahem, as part of new generation you can add some sample questions,
right, and you can add as many as you want,
you can even upload a CSV, and,
it will, will try to find the right match,
or the right, ah, uhm, uhm,
you can say text snippet out of all the documents in the
KB. And it tries to find that,
and tries to, basically, uhm,
like, associate with that, like, saves it, you know, for that question.
And it does that for, for,
uhm, all these questions, essentially,
right? And if it finds a match,
then it will just use this, uhm, this question as it is, and keeps
that match as well. So that match is, basically, this span,
you can say, right? You can see this has four spans.
Four span, basically means it's a character span.
So, basically, out of this one document,
it has, if you have seen the question, how to make LiveChat compliment all
these chatbots. Chatbots are great,
but let's face it, they sometimes need human help to deal with this,
to address this. We build a Zendesk LiveChat integration that lets your chatbot
seamlessly hand off conversation to an agent when user requests it.
In this article, we'll cover how to, so this is the part about how
our Zendesk LiveChat system works. And, uh, to input these fields,
first add, gambit,
collect, this, this,
this, right? So, you can see,
basically it is highlighting the character space.
the answer to this question lies,
right? So, now it's trying to make a,
like a, intelligent guess,
but it might not be accurate. And that is why we need a,
uh, uh, in the next version of it,
I will be making an edit option, where I can edit the,
uh, uh, uh,
question here and can even edit the span here.
And, uh, right now it has access to,
it basically gives the span from one document only,
but in the future I want to have, where it can give span from
multiple documents because if you think about it,
this question's answer can belong to multiple documents because LiveChat is a very big
feature of our product and it can have a lot of other information,
right? So,
uh, So,
we should have a capability to find all of those things,
those options, in a more liberal manner and then allow the user to be
able to trim down. I think that will be a good interface.
Again, these are like, feature ideas.
Make this process easy. Basically, the whole idea behind this,
making this dataset, and ideally you want to make a golden dataset of maybe
50 questions or 100 questions,
ideally more, depending on your question dataset.
And spend time on building this dataset so that you can really evaluate
how the system is working, how only that system is working.
And you can also use this dataset as a caching mechanism
as well maybe, so that if you have made these 100 questions,
right, corresponding, uhm,
character span in the documents,
and those are like gold dataset, and you know,
okay, those are accurate, and it will only change if the documents' content
change, uhm.
So, again,
there will be other stuff there as well to be looked at,
but, uhm, uhm,
so you can use that as a caching layer as well.
So, if somebody asks a question, you can use that as a question,
and it tries to match it against these 100 tests,
the question that I said you have, you have, like, manually created.
If it matches 20 of them with, uh, let's say,
90% accuracy, something like that,
then, uhm,
it basically picks the same answer but, you know, the exact down-to-earth,
essentially, character span that you've configured manually.
So that way, it's, uh,
like, it's very, uh,
I mean, it can increase the, uh, uhm, the accuracy
of the test retrieval. Much more dramatically,
because now you have a mechanism to improve it as you see problems,
so that in the future it's, it's resolved,
or even the past as well, it can be resolved as well,
if it's not accurate, and you can even go back to the system and,
uh, to the user and,
and make a correction, here this AI thing was not,
not correct, I verified it and this is the most correct answer.
So, and you can do that manually, possibly as well,
right? And that will be good. So,
uhm,
so let's take this part one and continue on the part two.