So,
let's continue. So, uhm,
so if by, uh, you have questions and you have ground truth,
essentially, right? And,
you have, uh,
ground truth basically, right? By ground truth, I mean, this character spans within a
document, right? Again, there can be things to improve it,
but right now, for one question,
you have character span from exactly one document,
not multiple documents. And,
at least, one span will be there, right? So, no question without a span,
because otherwise, it is no way to test it,
right? And, these spans are basically ground truth. This is what we want,
ideally, that we were to give as chunks,
right? So, this is the ideal thing. If they give it exactly these things,
these characters or these tokens, that means they are the most accurate,
right? They are 100% accurate. And,
this is basically a token level comparison or evaluation,
you can say, essentially, right? So,
instead of a chunk level evaluation, which is very common in the industry right
now, but this is the, very clearly,
makes more sense because it's much more granular and you can compare it.
Check exactly token level, uhm,
relevance, right? So,
uhm,
once we have this dataset,
which is a question, which is a user question,
and corresponding retrieved character spans,
essentially, uhm, then that is the ground truth,
this is the ideal character span that should be returned as part of the
retrieval, knowledge retrieval. This is the tool, essentially,
which will be used by CX agent,
right? So,
uhm, so that way we can test different,
different retrieval, so, uhm, in different configuration and see which
one is giving us the correct a really good result,
essentially, right? So, example,
uh, so this happens.
So, again, yeah, this is, so, this video is about basically how to generate
this. So, the way I'll just quickly talk about how it works.
So, first configuration is the real-time So,
these are something that you will extract typically from your human live chat,
uh, agent, uh, conversation transcripts,
right? So, either in chat conversations or maybe if you have calls,
then you call transcripts, right? Uh,
so, at the chat, live chat, uh, human live chat,
uh, conversation transcripts or the call transcripts.
Yeah, that's mostly that we do there, right? So,
from those, those are mostly conversations and even that is something,
uh, we have made in a,
made in a, knowledge base, which is to analyze conversations.
So, I'll not show this data right now.
Again, I'll not go into this because it's, uh,
customer's data. So,
uhm,
but I think it'll be good. to show it in a different video.
But basically, again, not going into that detail right now.
But basically, this, uh, first configuration is about rear-wall questions.
And these are basically single questions that the user has asked in the course
of the conversation, right? So, it's not, uh, So,
ideally, you would want to, like, go through the conversation and extract the specific
questions that the user has asked, which,
essentially, you want to test against, right?
So, basically, these are, like, uh, uhm,
which are, like, factual kind of questions, not factual questions, but, basically,
it requires a knowledge retrieval, essentially, right? You have to handpick those,
or you can, basically, have a system which will extract it automatically.
So, for that, something I have been doing, extract this kind of intel from
the live chat transcript, uhm,
but, maybe, initially, you can
just do it handpicked, you know, by self. Again, I just copied it, right
now, from our own live chat, that we have sitting on our website.
So, uhm, but, uh, not on the website,
but on the product page internally,
this is internal. So,
I have 30 questions here,
and the idea here is that, uhm, if you, uh, have, uh,
these questions.
I think I mentioned already that you can have a.
You should try to find the answers, or the,
or the basic character spans from the KB documents,
and if it can find it, it will use it.
Otherwise, the rest of the questions, it will not add in the dataset that
is, it is supposed to create, So, let's say I have 30,
and I think, I've already generated this.
You can see there are 25, I can generate again,
but I'll do the rest of the conditions, then I'll generate. So,
out of those 30, 20, it was able to find 25,
uh, character spans, obviously,
in the other, other documents, so, and each of those documents,
uhm, questions, it has tagged as real world.
So, these are, basically, it takes the questions exactly as it is,
right, uhm, if it can find the maps.
For the rest of it, if it cannot find, it will skip it.
So, it is, it will skip that five questions.
But even after that, it still only generates 25 questions.
I asked it to generate, actually, 50 questions.
Sometimes, it was not able to find the character span.
So, it, basically, removes those questions.
So, that's why it has generated 48. I have to fix it. So,
it always generates 50 questions. I have to put some extra return mechanisms there.
But I asked it to generate 50 questions. Right now,
it generates 25. It still has to generate 23 questions right now.
So, for that, it uses the next dimension,
which is, ah, where you can add a dimension.
Ah, for different combination of corresponding value for, ah, like,
generating these questions in a,
in a, ah,
like, synthetic manner. So, basically,
what it will do, here you can see, it has UserPersona as NewUser and
PowerUser. So,
ah, if I'm making an internal sub-customer support chatbot,
so, there'll be two type of people will be there. Ah, I can have
more personas with them. So, it will take a,
for example, NewUser, and then it will take,
ah, QueryIntent to be maybe integration help,
right, and then QueryComplexity will take basic, right, because NewUser with advanced query, ah,
will be, you know, less likely. So, it will probably remove those combination.
it doesn't make sense. It doesn't have something which doesn't make sense.
Ah, maybe in one of these languages or whom,
and then, ah, product area,
you know, some, something to may be late to analytics or something and it
will give all this information and basically it will have something like a prompt.
It will say something like, hey, this is a document which has a lot
of this information, whatever, function read through it.
I want you to create maybe
two questions based on
these different combinations,
you can pick whatever, combination of different,
you know, criteria like user-persona, query intent,
complexity level. So, I want you to create questions from these different combinations,
these two combinations which I am giving you, and,
uhm, uhm, uhm,
and create a question in such a way that the answer to that questions
can be taken from the text snippets from this document.
and make sure it is comprehensive and it is make sure it's,
uh, it completely answers the question,
right, so it's something like that, right. Right now,
again, it takes it from one document as well. I think the next version
will have some capability of multiple document,
uh, ground truth, uh, you know, that.
So, right now, it's just one document. So, this is what this, basically, uh,
configuration does, which is dimension-driven, we call it. Basically,
we create different dimensions, create a value to it, and it figures out different
problems. You can add more dimensions to it, right? You can,
uh, delete value, you can add value.
So,
all those things you can do. And then, finally,
in the preference, these things are extra there,
like, what is the tone on which the question you want to have,
right? And any focus area that you want to keep,
you can have that. So, it's an extra information.
And these things are there, like, question types, like, if it's a factual question,
if it's a... So, again, these are, like, parameters for you to generate completely
new questions, essentially, right? So, these are things which will help you get started.
But ultimately, you should ideally review all of those,
and if you're really serious about using the dataset, then review all the questions
and, uh, corresponding answers to that or the chunks or the character spans from
the documents, and edit that as well, which is something that Cable TV will,
which will bring in it. So that you have a,
and spend some time there, it's okay to spend some time here.
Think about the question that you were asked. I think it's a really good
way to really get in the user's mind.
And this will really help you build a dataset, which will be which you
can rely on, essentially, right? But if a retriever is giving good value,
good result for this particular dataset, then that retriever is really good,
right? So,
uhm, so it's worth spending,
you know, good time, a little bit of time here.
And, uhm, then, finally, you can put,
go to reviews, uh, step,
where, I mean,
you can review this previous configuration and you have a option to increase the
number, like, put a number of questions, right?
And maximum you can put 200 questions.
Start with one. I would recommend to start less,
maybe, maybe put 20 questions initially. And then see,
because question generation takes time,
right? Uhm, and it takes, you know,
I mean, it takes time, essentially. And use the tokens,
obviously, right? So, uh, I'll start with 20,
maybe, and let it generate.
And you can also change priority of these documents as well.
By default, everyone has same priority.
So, I mean,
it has some calculation. I think it remains the same as it was in
the last document. We can improve upon that as well.
But if I increase the priority of this document,
you can see it became 5. Or even increase further,
it remains 5. But if I increase this one,
it gets 4 for it. So,
uh, so that means that for these 6 documents,
4 questions will be generated from this document, 4 will be from this,
3 will be from this. If I want to, let's say,
remove, let's say, I
remove, I want to deprioritize this one,
then only one question will be generated,
right? So this is an extra thing that you want to use,
if you want to use to prioritize which documents are more
important for your, that's it, that's it, that's it,
that's it. And then you can click on Create or Generate,
it will then start doing it, you can see it is in preparing,
preparation stage, number of documents and questions,
how many documents are processed, how many questions are generated,
it will be visible here, you can see here, it started coming.
And,
it found some of these, you can see this was the,
if you remember, this was one of the messages from the user questions,
right? So again, you can see this is not a question exactly,
very cryptic. We have a URL example.
I'm not that cryptic, but, uh,
but that's how users will say things,
right? They will just say stuff, uhm,
that, uh, you have to be prepared for. That's why real-world questions,
grounding is the most important one, and you should really try to get real-world
questions. Because that will just improve the quality of your dataset.
So I think you can see here, it was able to generate to 14
questions or something, yeah. So yeah,
there's something I think I need to fix. Uhm,
uh, what happens is, I think, yeah, if this number of documents are less,
it is not able to find the questions,
answers, right? So you need to have your KB,
like, with a lot of documents, then it will work well.
Because, for example, I've added 30 questions,
right, in here. 30 questions,
and it was able to find match for only 11 of these,
right? I have to, I asked you to generate 20 questions,
right? Most of you should have found the answers to maybe 18
of them, because, uhm, those questions
answers will be there in my full documentation,
right? So that's why it's less. And because it's not able to find answers,
it is, uhm,
like, failing to, you find the corresponding spans,
and that's why, you know, it's, uh, it's less.
Less, right, uhm, than what you asked.
But, again, anyways, you can see out of 14,
11 are, uh, real-world questions and corresponding span.
And this is the place I'd leave you, want to review and edit stuff,
right? So I would definitely be adding the edit feature next.
This is the most important one, and this is a place,
You get to spend some time to do things. You can add more stuff
as well here, right? So I think this will be a nice view.
In the rendered view, you can just highlight something,
and it will just say, you know, add to this thing, or add to
something like that. Uh, yeah, I think this
will be interesting. And here you can just edit the portion as it were
itself, or make it a model or whatever. And,
uh, once it's done, maybe it will have a tag,
which is, modified or something or whatever,
so that user knows, you know, this is something they've done with it.
So, uh,
and you can see that it has generated these four extra questions.
Again, I'm not going to read through it. This is the work which ideally
the domain experts should be able to, should be spending time to make sure
it's done in a good way.
And that's it. Uhm, next up,
basically, very quickly, if I can talk about in the retriever system,
first of all, you can create new retrievers, you know, like this,
basically. And each of the retrievers, so I'll talk about this in the next
video, where you can see,
again, this is six documents, KB, small KB,
but you can see, uh, the document information and you can see how chunking
happened, you can do some querying.
You have a playground here, so you can inspect overall what happened in the
retriever, just so that you understand,
uh, what's going on.
And then there's an experiment mode, where,
uh, you can create new experiments,
give a name to it. Select a dataset that you have created earlier,
which is the old dataset that you are, you know, working on.
Then you can select one or multiple retrievers.
And then you can, uh, you know,
have these little pooled values. I can talk about that,
what is recall, what expression means. And these are just derivatives of these two.
But basically these are the two main ones. And there is a ranking formula
as well, which I will talk about again, selecting weighted sum of these two
values. Uhm,
again, things can be improved here, but this is what we have right now.
I can give a name and I can select a dataset.
Let's say on that dataset itself I have created, so let's say Experiment2Map,
let's say. And I click on
what I selected. Let me select all five videos.
All of them actually. Right.
Whatever. Otherwise it will just take a lot of time.
Oh, let me do that. Yes. So,
create experiment. So,
it's, what it is doing, there are seven retrievers, essentially.
And, uh, you can see that right now evaluation
is going on. And what it will do is,
it will, ah, use each of these retrievers on the same kb against
that question that is set. And it will,
each of the questions here that you have seen,
like for this 14 questions data set, it has a,
uh, ground truth. These are the characteristics, but it has a ground truth,
which is the actual correct value for it, right?
So in the retrievers experiment, you can see what it
is doing is it is, uh,
using this retriever, the OpenCLOS style retriever,
which has some configuration of its own,
it will, this is it.
basically get the chunks for the corresponding questions,
each question in this data set. This is the data set name,
unified whatever, uh, timestamp.
So, uhm, we have to improve the name of this data set as well.
But, uhm,
it will, uh, do this.
Get the chunks and then it will compare it with the
ground truth and depending on how much exact overlap,
you know, that it got from the ground truth value,
it will basically, uh, uhm, calculate these values essentially,
So you can see here right now it is doing this because we have
added a lot of, uh, these things. So now you can see it has,
uh, done evaluation for these two retrievers and it found that the hyper,
height, dense is, has a recall of 18.4%
and this one has, uh, it has added a third one.
So what it is doing is basically generating the recall and precision value and
final score which is the weighted sum of these two to give a final
ranking to these retrievers. And,
uh, yeah, so it's right now doing this right now it did 3,
uh, 4 actually and as it does if it finds
a better ranking it will update it here, right?
So this way I can really measure how
really, you know, how good the,
the retriever is working. If this percentage is 100 percent then that is the
best retriever against that dataset, against the old dataset.
So, so that is the,
that is the idea. Uhm, yeah.
And now we can go back and create better retrievers,
test it, and see, and make sure the old dataset is also good.
So, you know, see how it works out. Again,
I can go deeper into this thing, but this is just how this
experiment worked out. And that's it,
you know, that's the whole idea of, you know, this overall system basically helps
you evaluate against multiple retrievers.
Basically evaluate different different retrievers against one specific gold dataset of your questions
and ground truth and generate a value.
Again, it's a,
not really a complete, uhm,
100% accurate, even if you get 100% accurate here,
you know, obviously in the real world it will fail,
because, uh, you can ask a new question completely,
you know, which it has no idea, but if you have made a really
good diverse question dataset, then it will, uh,
basically get very close to serving most of the users,
essentially, right? So that's the idea, right? So now you can see it has
completed it, and it found that this BM25 rank,
re-ranked, is the best retriever, which has 21.5% recall,
which is not that great. So this definitely requires,
uhm, like, improvement on the KB side of things,
because I think KB is missing a lot of documents,
because it's a very small document. But if I have a bigger KB with
a lot of documents, I think it should work Try on this.
I'm not sure if I have any
triggers. Yeah,
so right now I don't have it. I think I should try it on
this one. And I think, and we'll even compare the results,
right? So yeah, that is the whole idea.
Uhm. Mostly I wanted to spend time on this about,
uh, how to, uh,
do question generation. And I think I covered this algorithm that I've been working
on, I've been using. And I built the system.
So if you want to try it out, it's all been live.
Uh, I'll share the link.
And it's an open source project. You can,
uh, with MIT license, you can actually use it.
You can build stuff on top of it if you want. Uh,
feel free and share your thoughts. And, uh,
uh, I mean, if you want,
you can, you can, uh, share in PR as well.
But, uh, yeah. I mean,
I, I mean, I can take a look. Uh, but, uh,
feel free to submit that. But, uh,
give any feedback. I think that's the point, right?
You can use this project. You can run it by yourself.
You need a convex, uh, instance to do that.
But rest, you can just run it by yourself. Anyways,
that's a thing I wanted to share.
I will make a more crisp video out of this for almost 34 minutes
of rant.